ezinescroll.com 2012-12-07

# Privacy - EzineScroll Articles

**Privacy Policy**

**General**

EzineScroll.com of NeoGeo Pty Ltd takes your privacy seriously. We utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the personal information that we collect and receive through our websites. We value your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence, so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to family and friends.

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any significant changes to this Privacy Policy, will be posted on our websites. You may review a current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at the bottom of the home page of this website.

**Information We Collect and How It Is Used**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site  **EzineScroll.com**. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, operating system, browser usage and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

We use your personal information to:

  * provide our services
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;
  * customize the user experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;
  * communicate marketing and promotional offers to you;
  * do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

Information posted on EzineScroll.com is obviously publicly available. The users of our services may contact you by themselves via your email address and/or phone number if you provided in your posting. NeoGeo Pty Ltd declines all responsibilities for such contact and all results caused by such contact.

If you contact us directly by sending email to any address at our website domain names, or send comments through our website, your email address will be used if we reply to your comments or questions.

Please do not post or submit any personal information that you expect to keep private.

**Protecting your Privacy**

We do not sell or rent your personal data to anyone. The personal data you provide us is saved in a secure environment and is kept in our records. Information collected is stored in a single, secure database, accessible only by EzineScroll.com members. We employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies in order to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. Because this website is hosted by third party (web hosting provider), we cannot guarantee complete security.

Our websites, or users of our websites, may provide links to third party websites. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites. We encourage all users to read the privacy policies of all websites visited.

**Use of Cookies**

Our web server may set and access “cookies”, small text files placed on your hard drive, to keep track of the pages visited. The “cookies” do not reveal personal information, rather give us statistical data to help analyze our web page flow and measure effectiveness. By tracking the overall traffic patterns of our visitors, we can make the site more responsive to our visitors’ needs and interests. Using cookies is popular by many websites.

Third party websites made available by, or through, our websites, may also assign cookies. We do not control the use of cookies by third party websites, have any access to such cookies or to any information that they contain.

**Compliance with the Law**

We don’t sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety. By using this website you acknowledge and agree that NeoGeo Pty Ltd may, in its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your Content, as well as your information, such as email addresses, IP addresses, timestamps, and other user information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

  1. comply with legal process;
  2. enforce these Terms;
  3. respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third-parties;
  4. respond to claims that contact information (for example phone number, street address) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment;
  5. protect the rights, property, or personal safety of NeoGeo Pty Ltd, its users or the general public.

**A Special Note about Children**

We do not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 18. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use our websites unsupervised. If you are under the age of 18, you may use our websites only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. If we learn that a posting has been submitted by a person under the age of 18 without supervised, we will remove that post.

**Changes to our privacy policy**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. However, we advise that you check this page regularly to keep up to date with any necessary changes.

**Security.**  We use many tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. We can’t however guarantee the continuous functionality and liability of these tools at all times.
